<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Activity 2</string>
    <string name="delhi">Delhi, India’s capital territory, is a massive metropolitan area in the country’s north. In Old Delhi, a neighborhood dating to the 1600s, stands the imposing Mughal-era Red Fort, a symbol of India, and the sprawling Jama Masjid mosque, whose courtyard accommodates 25,000 people. Nearby is Chandni Chowk, a vibrant bazaar filled with food carts, sweets shops and spice stalls.</string>
    <string name="mumbai">Mumbai (formerly called Bombay) is a densely populated city on India’s west coast. A financial center, it\'s India\'s largest city. On the Mumbai Harbour waterfront stands the iconic Gateway of India stone arch, built by the British Raj in 1924. Offshore, nearby Elephanta Island holds ancient cave temples dedicated to the Hindu god Shiva. The city\'s also famous as the heart of the Bollywood film industry.</string>
    <string name="ahmedabad">Ahmedabad, in western India, is the largest city in the state of Gujarat. The Sabarmati River runs through its center. On the western bank is the Gandhi Ashram at Sabarmati, which displays the spiritual leader’s living quarters and artifacts. Across the river, the Calico Museum of Textiles, once a cloth merchant\'s mansion, has a significant collection of antique and modern fabrics.</string>
    <string name="bangalore">Bengaluru (also called Bangalore) is the capital of India\'s southern Karnataka state. The center of India\'s high-tech industry, the city is also known for its parks and nightlife. By Cubbon Park, Vidhana Soudha is a Neo-Dravidian legislative building. Former royal residences include 19th-century Bangalore Palace, modeled after England’s Windsor Castle, and Tipu Sultan’s Summer Palace, an 18th-century teak structure.</string>
    <string name="lucknow">Lucknow, a large city in northern India, is the capital of the state of Uttar Pradesh. Toward its center is Rumi Darwaza, a Mughal gateway. Nearby, the 18th-century Bara Imambara shrine has a huge arched hall. Upstairs, Bhool Bhulaiya is a maze of narrow tunnels with city views from its upper balconies. Close by, the grand Victorian Husainabad Clock Tower was built as a victory column in 1881.</string>
    <string name="hyderabad">Hyderabad is the capital of southern India\'s Telangana state. A major center for the technology industry, it\'s home to many upscale restaurants and shops. Its historic sites include Golconda Fort, a former diamond-trading center that was once the Qutb Shahi dynastic capital. The Charminar, a 16th-century mosque whose 4 arches support towering minarets, is an old city landmark near the long-standing Laad Bazaar.</string>
    <string name="chennai">Chennai, on the Bay of Bengal in eastern India, is the capital of the state of Tamil Nadu. The city is home to Fort St. George, built in 1644 and now a museum showcasing the city’s roots as a British military garrison and East India Company trading outpost, when it was called Madras. Religious sites include Kapaleeshwarar Temple, adorned with carved and painted gods, and St. Mary’s, a 17th-century Anglican church.</string>
    <string name="kolkata">Kolkata (formerly Calcutta) is the capital of India\'s West Bengal state. Founded as an East India Company trading post, it was India\'s capital under the British Raj from 1773–1911. Today it’s known for its grand colonial architecture, art galleries and cultural festivals. It’s also home to Mother House, headquarters of the Missionaries of Charity, founded by Mother Teresa, whose tomb is on site.</string>
    <string name="chennai_akariabeach">The shaanor amour-propre of Chennai, the famous Marina Beach, has been acclaimed as the second-longest beach in the world with a white sandy foreshore that looks as though exending to infinity. </string>
    <string name="chnnai_breezybeach">Breezy Beach lays in the remote and serene neighbourhood of Valmiki Nagar in Chennai. Being smaller and less polluted, its a perfect getaway for anyone looking for a peaceful evening. Read More</string>
    <string name="chennai_marinabeach">The sandy coastline begins from Ennore in the north extending south into Uthandi, leaving one to choose from more than just Marina and Elliot\'s beach.</string>
    <string name="chennai_marundeshwartemple">Marundeeswarar Temple, in Tiruvanmiyur, near Chennai has the temple deity Shiva in the form of Marundeeswar or Aushadeeswarar, the God of Medicines. </string>
    <string name="bangalore_mgroad">MG Road is one of a most popular shopping and entertainment hub of Bangalore. Swarming with people at almost all the time, one must visit the place if in Bangalore.</string>
    <string name="bangalore_lalbagh">The majestic Bangalore palace, enclosed by beautiful gardens, is a famous tourist attraction in Bangalore. It is now owned by the Mysore Royal family. Read More</string>
    <string name="bangalore_nationalpark">Housing the country\'s first butterfly park, this park has a huge variety of fauna, making it one of the most enjoyable tourist attractions in the city. Tourists can also opt for Safari rides through the park. </string>
    <string name="bangalore_palace">This botanical garden is a haven for all nature lovers. It was commissioned by Hyder Ali in 1760 and completed by Tipu Sultan, with a spread of 240 acres. </string>
    <string name="lucknow_chowk">Chowk market in Lucknow is one of those places of the city that are a window into its rich cultural heritage. Beginning from Chikan work to succulent kebabs, one can find it all at the Chowk market. Read More</string>
    <string name="lucknow_hazratganj">Hazratganj, the central shopping district of Lucknow, has a long history behind it and has undergone a great makeover that bridges the past and the present and continues to serve as Lucknow\'s central shopping arcade.</string>
    <string name="lucknow_imambara">The Bara Imambara of Lucknow is one of the most famous monuments of the city. Also known as Asfi Imambara, after the name of the Nawab of Lucknow who got it constructed, it is an important place of worship for the Muslims who come here every year to celebrate the religious festival of Muharram. </string>
    <string name="lucknow_zoo">The Prince of Wales Zoological Gardens was built in 1921 was built to commemorate the Royal family\'s visit to Lucknow.</string>
    <string name="hyderabad_charminar">Charminar is the most important landmark in the city of Hyderabad. The monument was erected when Quli Qutb Shah shifted his capital from Golcondo to Hyderabad. </string>
    <string name="hyderabad_chowmahallapalace">Once the seat of the Asaf Jahi dynasty, the Chowmahalla Palace was built in Hyderabad. It is located near the famous monument, Charminar and Laad Bazar. The palace is designed very intricately and holds that Nawabi Charm in itself.</string>
    <string name="hyderabad_husainlake">Hussain Sagar Lake is one of a largest man-made lake situated in Hyderabad. Renowned for its monolith of Lord Buddha placed right at the center of the lake, the place is famously known as a Tank Bund</string>
    <string name="hyderabad_golcondafort">Golconda Fort is a massive fortress whose ruins stand proudly even today displaying the glory of its rich past and some untold sagas of the city\'s history. </string>
    <string name="mumbai_colaba_market">Established by the East India company, Colaba causeway is a hub of shopping market for apparels, gadgets, accessories, footwear, etc. Along this street is an Afghan church and Sasson dock.</string>
    <string name="mumbai_elephanta_caves">14 kms from city center 11 out of 27 Places To Visit in Mumbai An UNESCO World Heritage Site, Elephanta Caves is a specimen of rock cut art and architecture from the times of medieval India. It is an island and is located at a distance of 11km from the city of Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="mumbai_gateway_of_india">The Jehangir Art Gallery, an art gallery in Mumbai, was founded by Sir Cowasji Jehangir at the request of K K Hebbar and Homi Bhabha. It was built in 1952. Managed by the Committee of Management, the entire cost of this mansion was donated by Cowasji Jehangir.</string>
    <string name="mumbai_juhu_beach">Besides Juhu and Girgaum Chowpatty, Mumbai has many beautiful and isolated beaches where one can spend some relaxed time and enjoy a date with their lovers or family holidays by renting cottages</string>
    <string name="kolkata_howrah_bridge">Located over the Hooghly river in West Bengal, Howrah Bridge or the Rabindra Setu is the main connection between Howrah and Kolkata. It is a cantilever bridge and is regarded as one of the busiest ones among them.</string>
    <string name="kolkata_indian_museum">The Indian Museum is one of the oldest museums of the world boasting some of the most exquisite collections of ornaments, fossils, skeletons, antiques, armors, mummies and stunning Mughal paintings.</string>
    <string name="kolkata_jorasanko_thakurbari">Currently located on the Rabindra Bharati University campus in Jorasank, Jorasanko Thakur Bari is the house in which the first non-European Nobel laureate and poet, Rabindranath Tagore was born.</string>
    <string name="kolkata_park_street">The glowing structure that adorns the streets of Kolkata is the popular Hindu Temple, Birla Temple. Dedicated to Lord Krishna and Radha, the temple is perfect specimen of craftsmanship.</string>
    <string name="ahmedabad_jumma_masjid">The Jama Masjid situated in Ahmedabad is one of the largest mosques in India built in the period of 1424 and was built by Emperor Sultan Ahmed Shah. </string>
    <string name="ahmedabad_sabarmati_ashram">Once the residence of Mahatma Gandhi and his wife Kasturba, this undoubtedly is the biggest tourist attraction situated in the suburb of Ahmedabad, Gujarat. Located on the tranquil and serene stretch of Sabarmati River it was also referred to as the \'Satyagraha Ashram\'  </string>
    <string name="ahmedabad_siddsayed_mosque">Built by Sidi Saeed or Sidi Saiyyed in 1573, as the name suggests, the Sidi Saiyyed Mosque, is one of the most famous mosques of Ahmedabad. The mosque is said to be built in the last year of the existence of the Sultanate of Gujarat.</string>
    <string name="ahmedabad_the_pols">A pol ( pronunciation (help. info), pronounced as pole, Gujarati: પોળ) in India is a housing cluster which comprises many families of a particular group, linked by caste, profession, or religion. Pols are typical of urban centres in Gujarat especially of Old Ahmedabad.</string>
    <string name="delhi_akshardham">Also known as the Delhi Akshardham, this temple complex was built in 2005 and sits deftly near the banks of River Yamuna.</string>
    <string name="delhi_gardenfivesenses">The Garden of Five Senses is a park spread over 20 acres, in Saidul Ajaib village, opposite Saket, near the Mehrauli heritage area in Delhi, India</string>
    <string name="delhi_hauzkhas">Well known in medieval times, the Hauz Khas village has amazing buildings built around the reservoir. There are remnants of Islamic architecture roughly colored by splotches of urban culture. </string>
    <string name="delhi_lotustemple">Commonly known as Lotus temple, it is a Houses of Worship, the Lotus Temple is open to all, regardless of religion, or any other distinction. It is situated near mandir marg in Kalkaji, New Delhi</string>
</resources>
